Guide to the Dial/Scofield Thayer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1895-1941; Series V; 11.5; (22 boxes)
  - Printed material
    - Pamphlets
      - Bertray, Dr.: "Aux victimes de l'amour", n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1590)
      - Garrett, A. E. and Tomalin, H. F.: "The Purpose and Efficacy of Clothing" (Box 58, Folder 1591)
      - L'Hermite, Tristan: "Le Promenoir de deux amans", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1592)
      - Keyserling, Hermann: "Deutschlands wahre politische mission" (Box 59, Folder 1593)
      - Mussorgsky: "Boris Godunov", 1910 (Box 59, Folder 1594)
      - "Schönbrunn, an English Guide", n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1595)
    - Pictures, 1927, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1596)
    - Playbills and programs
      - Apollo-theater, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1597)
      - Bayerischen Staatstheater, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 1598)
      - Deutsches Theaters, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1599)
      - Grosses Schauspielhaus, 1925
      - Komishe Oper: Berlin, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1600)
      - Operntheater, 1925-26 (Box 59, Folder 1601)
      - Raimund Theater, 1925-26 (Box 59, Folder 1602)
      - Staatstheater, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 1603)
      - Strauss Theater, 1926
      - Theater in Admiralspalast, 1925-26 (Box 59, Folder 1604)
      - Theater in Josefstadt, 1925 (Box 59, Folder 1605)
      - Theater in der Königgrätzerstrasse, 1926 (Box 59, Folder 1606)
      - Theater in Redoutensall der Höfburg, n.d.
      - Theater an der Wein
    - Vocabulary lists, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1607)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 1608)
  - School papers: Bancroft School
    - Artwork, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1609)
    - Notebooks: English IV, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1610)
    - Notebooks: History I-III, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1611-13)
    - Notebook: unidentified, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1614)
    - Papers, 1903-05, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1615-19)
    - Printed material: The Historian, 1903-06 (Box 60, Folder 1620-24)
    - Report cards, 1903-04 (Box 60, Folder 1625)
    - Scrapbook: "A Pictorial History of America"
      See: Oversize, Box 75, folder 1954
    - Writings
      - "Do I Believe?", 1905 (Box 60, Folder 1626)
      - "A Legend of Old Italy" (Box 60, Folder 1627)
      - "Port Arthur", [1905] (Box 60, Folder 1628)
      - "Russia", [1905] (Box 60, Folder 1629-33)
      - "Yeko: the Story of a Japanese Boy", 1901 (Box 60, Folder 1634-35)
      - "A Young Scottish Knight", 1903 (Box 60, Folder 1636)
  - School Papers: Milton Academy
    - Algebra papers, 1905, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1637-38)
    - English tests, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1639)
    - English themes, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1640-42)
      See also: Oversize, Box 75, folder 1955
    - French papers, n,d (Box 61, Folder 1643)
    - Geometry notes, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1644)
    - German papers, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1645)
    - Greek notes, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1646)
    - History papers, 1905, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1647-50)
    - Latin tests, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1651)
    - Latin translation, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1652)
    - Miscellaneous exercises, 1905-07, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1653-54)
    - Printed Material
      - The Milton Orange and Blue, 1903-1906 Jun (Box 61, Folder 1655-60)
      - The Milton Orange and Blue, 1906 Oct-1908 (Box 62, Folder 1661-64)
      - Milton Graduates Bulletin, 1927 Oct (Box 62, Folder 1665)
    - Sports awards, 1906-07 (Box 62, Folder 1666)
  - School Papers: Harvard College
    - Class day essay: "Marlowe's Dr. Faustus ", 1913 (Box 62, Folder 1667)
    - Class day programs, 1913 (Box 62, Folder 1668-69)
    - "English 5", 1913, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1670-74)
    - "English 5: Shelley, or the Poetic Value of Revolutionary Principles", 1913, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1675-76)
    - "English 14", 1911 (Box 62, Folder 1677)
    - "English 31", 1909-10, n,d (Box 62, Folder 1678-81)
    - "English 31", n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1682-83)
    - "English: Passages of Shakespeare Learned by Heart", 1911-12 (Box 63, Folder 1684)
    - French notes, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1685)
    - Greek notes, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1686)
    - "Philosophy: Section IV", 1911 (Box 63, Folder 1687-90)
    - [Philosophy?], 1911, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1691-92)
    - Physics, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1693)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous notes (Box 63, Folder 1694-98)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous notes (Box 64, Folder 1699-1704)
    - Printed material
      - Harvard Advocate, 1906, 1912 (Box 64, Folder 1705-06)
      - Harvard Lampoon, 1909-10 (Box 64, Folder 1707)
      - Harvard Monthly, 1916 Jan (Box 64, Folder 1708)
    - Sports scores, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1709)
    - Submissions to college magazines, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1710-14)
  - School Papers: Oxford University
    - Classics notes, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1715)
    - Heretics essay: "Compton Mackenzie", n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1716)
    - Philosophy papers, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1717-21)
  - Secretarial applications, 1923-24 (Box 65, Folder 1722-28)
  - Telegram drafts, 1923-24 (Box 65, Folder 1729-30)
  - Writings: Juvenile Poetry
    - "Milton verse et circa", 1903-07, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1731-33)
    - "Summer 1909", 1909, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1734-37)
    - Harvard College
      - "English 5", n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1738)
      - "English 16", 1912 (Box 65, Folder 1739)
      - "English 31", n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1740-43)
      - "Harvard Verse", 1909-13, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1744-53)
      - "Submissions to the Harvard Monthly ", 1910-13, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1754-57)
      - Typescript of college verse, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1758-59)
  - Writings: Poetry
    - "And Love Said, Let There Be Rain" (Box 66, Folder 1760-61)
    - "Le Cantique des desirs inassouvis", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1762)
    - "Chanson arrogante", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1763)
    - "Chanson banale", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1764)
    - "Chanson eperdue", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1765)
    - "Chanson equivoque", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1766)
    - "Chanson gaie", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1767)
    - "Chanson illusoire", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1768)
    - "Chanson Maladive", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1769)
    - "Chanson merveilleuse", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1770)
    - "Chevaux du bois", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1771)
    - "Des choses qu'il convient de lancer au printemps", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1773)
    - "Counsel to a Young Man", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1774)
    - "Crow Song: for Texas Wilson", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1775)
    - "Dawn from a Railway Day-coach", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1776)
    - "Day" (Box 66, Folder 1777)
    - "The Elder Poet", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1778)
    - "False Light", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1779)
    - "For Fritz Klatt, and his Friends, and Mine" (Box 66, Folder 1780)
    - "Gentlefolk", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1781)
    - "I Walk, Understandingly" (Box 66, Folder 1782)
    - "In Evil Time", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1783)
    - "In which the Fingers of the Night Wind Are Made to Call" (Box 66, Folder 1784)
    - "In which the Poet Remembers HImself", n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1785)
    - "Jesus Again", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1786-87)
    - "Leo Arrogans", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1788-89)
    - "On a Crucifix", 1926, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1790-91)
    - "On an Old Painting in Portsmouth Harbor Reproduced in The Dial, and Perused in Europe by an Expatriate. For Alyse Gregory." (Box 67, Folder 1792)
    - "On the Mask of a Poet Recently Young", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1793)
    - "Poème sage", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1794)
    - "Poèmes avengles", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1795)
    - "The Poet, the Exponent of the Heart, Takes Leave", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1796)
    - "Poets I Have Loved so Deeply", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1797)
    - "Rarement", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1798)
    - "A Song with Questions", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1799)
    - "Spleen Anglais", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1800)
    - "To One who Was Betrayed", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1801)
    - "To the Acting Editor of The Dial ", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1802)
    - "When we Have Quit the Ocean's Treacherous Thronging", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1803)
    - "Wherefore", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1804)
    - Fragments and notes, n.s. (Box 67, Folder 1805-06)
    - Unidentified manuscripts, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1807-08)
    - "Scofield's unpublished poems": typescript and carbon (Box 67, Folder 1809-10)
    - Galleys, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1811-12)
    - Dial publication scrapbook, 1925-27 (Box 67, Folder 1813-21)
  - Writings: Prose
    - "Arthur Schnitzler", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1822-23)
    - "Berlin Letter", 1926 (Box 67, Folder 1824-26)
    - "An International Episode", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1827)
    - "A Mid-Winter's Study Hour Dream", n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1828)
    - "To the Editors of The Dial ": unpublished version, 1925 (Box 67, Folder 1829)
    - "To the Editors of The Dial ": published version, 1925 (Box 67, Folder 1830)
    - Unidentified and miscellaneous prose (Box 67, Folder 1831-34)
  - Writings of Others
    - Bryant, Louise: Poems
      See: Box 28, folder 750
    - Chanler, Alita: "A Clog-Dance", n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1835)
    - Chapman, John Jay: "The Treason and Death of Benedict Arnold." Typescript, corrected, signed., 1910 (Box 68, Folder 1836)
    - Harwood, H. Cecil: "Two Views of Oxford", n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1837)
    - Jerome, Helen: "The Cry of the Woman", n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1838)
    - Lowell, Amy: wager with Thayer, 1920 (Box 68, Folder 1839)
    - Marble, Annie Russell: "Literature Lectures", 1895 (Box 68, Folder 1840)
    - Marconnier, Byrne: Poems, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1841)
    - Moore, Marianne: galley proofs of her work, annotated by Scofield Thayer, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1842)
    - Nichol, Robert Taylor: manuscripts, 1917-20, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1843-47)
    - Parr, Robert: Poems, 1915, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1848)
    - Scofield, J. M.: 1848 newsletter transcriptions, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1849)
    - Wright, Cuthbert: "The End of It" (Box 68, Folder 1850)
    - Unidentified typescript, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1851-53)
  - Y.M.C.A. papers, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1854-55)
- Artwork, 1917-82; Series VI; 3.75; (5 boxes)
  Boxes 69-73 contain Series VI. Papers relating to
  Scofield Thayer's art collection have been arranged
  alphabetically by topic and then by type of material.
  The final three boxes of the series contain blocks
  for illustrations, unarranged.
  - Dial Collection
    - Bills and receipts
      - "A" general, 1921 (Box 69, Folder 1856)
      - Amsler and Ruthardt, 1920-24 (Box 69, Folder 1857)
      - "B" general, 1922, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1858)
      - Bernheim Jeune et cie., 1923 (Box 69, Folder 1859)
      - Galerie Caspari, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1860)
      - Paul Cassirer, 1922-25
      - Charles Daniel Paintings, 1925 (Box 69, Folder 1861)
      - Adolf Dehn, 1922
      - J. Deibler, 1921
      - Galerie van Diemen, 1922
      - Galerie Drouet, 1923 (Box 69, Folder 1862)
      - Ducart, 1921-22
      - Galerie Alfred Flechtheim, 1921-25 (Box 69, Folder 1863)
      - "G" general, 1917-22 (Box 69, Folder 1864)
      - Paul Graupe Antiquariat, 1922 (Box 69, Folder 1865)
      - Hugo Heller, 1920-24 (Box 69, Folder 1866)
      - Max Hevesi, 1923 (Box 69, Folder 1867)
      - Hugo von Hofmannsthal, n.d.
      - Independent Gallery, 1923 (Box 69, Folder 1868)
      - "J-K" general, 1923-24 (Box 69, Folder 1869)
      - Richard Lanyi, 1921-23 (Box 69, Folder 1870)
      - Leceister Galleries, 1921-23
      - "M" general, 1921-23 (Box 69, Folder 1871)
      - Mareès-Gesellschaft, 1922-26 (Box 69, Folder 1872)
      - N. E. Montross, 1918-20 (Box 69, Folder 1873)
      - "N" general, 1921-23 (Box 69, Folder 1874)
      - "R" general, 1922-23 (Box 69, Folder 1875)
      - Paul Rosenberg, 1923-24 (Box 69, Folder 1876)
      - "S" general, 1921-23 (Box 69, Folder 1877)
      - Scott and Forbes, 1917-20 (Box 69, Folder 1878)
      - Galerie Simon, 1922-23 (Box 69, Folder 1879)
      - Kunstverlag Wulfrum, 1921-22 (Box 69, Folder 1880)
      - Wurthle and Sohn, 1921-23 (Box 69, Folder 1881)
      - Unidentified, 1920-23, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1882)
    - Correspondence
      - Japanese prints, 1935-39 (Box 69, Folder 1883)
      - Loan requests, 1936-82 (Box 69, Folder 1884-86)
    - Customs declaration, 1922 (Box 69, Folder 1887)
    - Insurance policy, 1921 (Box 69, Folder 1888)
    - Lists of artwork, 1923-25, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1889-93)
  - Living Art: exhibition
    - Announcement by Worcester Art Museum, 1924, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 1894)
    - Insurance policy, 1924 (Box 69, Folder 1895)
    - List of artwork, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1896)
    - Offers of the exhibition, 1924 (Box 69, Folder 1897)
  - Living Art: portfolio
    - Notes for text, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1898-99)
    - Draft (Box 69, Folder 1900-03)
    - "Carbon of folio text", n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1904-06)
    - [Mock-up], n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1907)
    - Publication announcement, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1908)
    - Reviews, 1924-26 (Box 70, Folder 1909-10)
    - Final inventory, 1929 (Box 70, Folder 1911)
    - Unidentified typescript, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1912)
  - Original Artworks
    - Cummings, E. E.
      - Study for "Dancing Girl, Leaning Right": Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1912a)
      - [Untitled]: embracing nude couple. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1912b)
      - [Untitled]: female nude posing. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1912c)
      - [Untitled]: standing female nude. Ink on paper (Box 70, Folder 1912)
      - [Untitled]: sketches of nude women. Pencil on paper, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1912e)
        See also: Oversize, Boxes 76 and 76a
    - Dehn, Adolf
      See: Oversize, Boxes 76 and 76a
    - Kronberg, Sascha
      See: Oversize, Box 76a
    - Unidentified
      See: Oversize, Box 76
  - Miscellaneous
    - Illustrations, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1913-33)
    - Woodblocks, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1934)
    - Woodblocks, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1935)
    - Woodblocks, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1936)
- Oversize, 6.25; (4 boxes)
  Oversize contains materials from Series II,
  III, IV, V, and VI. The entry for each item
  indicates the box and folder number where
  it is housed, since certain items are not
  arranged in strict hierarchical order.
  - OFFICE FILES
    - Posters and clipsheets (Box 74, Folder 1937-38)
    - "Americana" file clippings, 1924, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1939-41)
    - Accounts for Dial Press, 1924 (Box 74, Folder 1942)
  - DIAL MANUSCRIPTS
    - Hofmannsthal, Hugo von: "Vienna Letter", 1928 (Box 74, Folder 1943)
    - Pound, Ezra: "The Fourth Canto." Annotated; privately printed (Box 76a, Folder 1973)
    - Smith, Logan Pearsall: "Laconics", 1928 (Box 74, Folder 1945)
    - Smith, Logan Pearsall: "Queen Victoria", 1921 (Box 74, Folder 1946)
  - SCOFIELD THAYER CORRESPONDENCE
    - Dehn, Adolf: Illustrated letters, 1923, 1924 (Box 76a, Folder 1974)
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - "80 Washington Square": blueprints, 1917 (Box 76a, Folder 1975)
    - Harvard Monthly editors, 1913 (Box 74, Folder 1948)
    - Unidentified man, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1949-51)
    - Unidentified woman [Mura?], n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1952)
    - Handbill concerning General Strike of Paper Box Makers Union, 1919 (Box 74, Folder 1953)
    - Scrapbook: "A Pictorial History of America", 1903 (Box 75, Folder 1959)
    - "Life" (Box 74, Folder 1954)
    - The Milton Record (2 issues), 1906, 1907 (Box 74, Folder 1955)
    - Harvard Class Album, 1913 (Box 75, Folder 1960)
    - Harvard Crimson, 1916 (Box 74, Folder 1956)
    - Newspaper clipping, 1914 (Box 74, Folder 1957)
    - Y.M.C.A. newspaper, 1916 (Box 74, Folder 1958)
  - ARTWORK
    - Scrapbook, 1919-24, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1961)
    - Illustrations (reproductions collected by Thayer), n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1962)
    - Cummings, E. E.
      - ["Dancers"]: Ink on paper, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 1986)
      - ["Dancing Girl, Leaning Left"]. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1963)
      - ["Dancing Girl, Leaning Right"]. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1964)
      - ["Figure"]: Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 76a, Folder 1976)
      - ["Nude"]: Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 76a, Folder 1977)
      - ["Standing Nude in Profile"]: Ink on paper (Box bsd, folder 1987)
      - [Untitled]: female nude. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 1988)
      - [Untitled]: female studies. Pencil on paper, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1965)
      - [Untitled]: male and female grotesque dancing. Ink on paper (Box 76, Folder 1966)
      - [Untitled]: matatdor with bull. Ink and wash on paper (Box 76a, Folder 1978)
      - [Untitled]: sketches of nude females. Pencil on paper, n.d. (Box 76a, Folder 1979)
      - [Untitled]: woman with arms outstretched. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 1989)
    - Dehn, Adolf
      - "Giraffe": caricature of standing woman. Ink on paper, signed, 1922 (Box bsd, folder 1990)
      - "Lovers": man and woman, seated. Ink on paper, signed, 1923 (Box 76, Folder 1967)
      - "Mother and Daughter": Ink on paper, signed "Dolphin" (Box 76, Folder 1968)
      - "Wise and Foolish Virgins": Ink on paper, signed, 1924 (Box bsd, folder 1991)
      - [Untitled]: woman embracing chair. Ink on paper, signed, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1969)
      - [Untitled]: female figures intertwined. Ink on paper, signed, 1923 (Box 76a, Folder 1980)
        Sketch of woman's head on reverse.
      - [Untitled]: woman dancing. Ink on paper, signed, 1923 (Box 76a, Folder 1981)
        Sketch of couple reclining on
        couch on reverse.
      - [Untitled]: portrait of woman wearing shawl. Ink on textured paper, signed, 1921 (Box 76a, Folder 1982)
    - Kronberg, Sascha
      - [Untitled]: woman mourning over graveyard. Pencil on paper, signed, n.d. (Box 76a, Folder 1983)
      - [Untitled]: reclining female nude. Pencil on paper, signed, n.d. (Box 76a, Folder 1984)
      - [Untitled]: kneeling female nude. Pencil on paper, signed, n.d. (Box 76a, Folder 1985)
    - Unidentified
      - [Untitled]: woman standing in profile. Ink on paper (Box 76, Folder 1970)
      - [Untitled]: woman and man's legs. Ink on paper (Box 76, Folder 1971)
      - [Untitled]: embracing figures in contrast. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1972)
      - [Untitled]: female nudes. Ink on paper, n.d. (Box bsd, folder 1992)
        Two sketches mounted in one mat.
- Formerly Restricted Papers, 1912-1931; 2.29; (6 boxes)
  The papers in Boxes 77-82 were restricted until
  May 24, 2012.
  - Orr, Elaine: letters from Scofield Thayer, 1912-1915 (Box 77, Folder 1993-2006)
  - Orr, Elaine: letters from Scofield Thayer, 1916 January-May (Box 78, Folder 2007-28)
  - Orr, Elaine: letters from Scofield Thayer, 1916 May 26-1918 June 14 (Box 79, Folder 2029-56)
  - Orr, Elaine: letters from Scofield Thayer, 1918 June 15-1925, undated (Box 80, Folder 2057-68)
  - Beck, Thomas H., 1925 May 11 (Box 80, Folder 2069)
  - Cummings, E. E.: letter to Scofield Thayer, undated (Box 80, Folder 2070)
  - Thayer, Florence: letters from Scofield Thayer, 1925 June-July, undated (Box 80, Folder 2071)
  - Thayer, Scofield: letter to Alyse Gregory, 1922 January 9 (Box 80, Folder 2072)
  - Thayer, Scofield: letter drafts to Charles M. Thayer and the Worcester Police Department, 1930-1931 (Box 80, Folder 2073)
  - Thayer, Scofield: order to appear in Probate Court, 1930 October 1 (Box 80, Folder 2074)
  - Notepads, undated (Box 80, Folder 2075-2079)
  - Notepads, undated (Box 81, Folder 2079-85)
  - Notepads, undated (Box 82, Folder 2086)
  - Pocket notebooks, 1921 November-1926 October, undated (Box 82, Folder 2087-2092)
- Restricted Fragile, 4.8; (12 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 83-94: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 1 (Box 83, Folder 2093)
  - Box 1, folder 2 (Box 83, Folder 2094)
  - Box 1, folder 3 (Box 83, Folder 2095)
  - Box 1, folder 4 (Box 83, Folder 2096)
  - Box 1, folder 5 (Box 83, Folder 2097)
  - Box 1, folder 6 (Box 83, Folder 2098)
  - Box 1, folder 7 (Box 83, Folder 2099)
  - Box 1, folder 8 (Box 83, Folder 2100)
  - Box 1, folder 9 (Box 83, Folder 2101)
  - Box 1, folder 10 (Box 83, Folder 2102)
  - Box 1, folder 11 (Box 83, Folder 2103)
  - Box 1, folder 12 (Box 83, Folder 2104)
  - Box 1, folder 13 (Box 83, Folder 2105)
  - Box 1, folder 14 (Box 83, Folder 2106)
  - Box 1, folder 15 (Box 83, Folder 2107)
  - Box 1, folder 16 (Box 83, Folder 2108)
  - Box 1, folder 17 (Box 83, Folder 2109)
  - Box 1, folder 18 (Box 83, Folder 2110)
  - Box 1, folder 19 (Box 83, Folder 2111)
  - Box 1, folder 20 (Box 83, Folder 2112)
  - Box 1, folder 22 (Box 83, Folder 2113)
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 83, Folder 2114)
  - Box 1, folder 24 (Box 83, Folder 2115)
  - Box 1, folder 25 (Box 83, Folder 2116)
  - Box 1, folder 26 (Box 83, Folder 2117)
  - Box 1, folder 27 (Box 83, Folder 2118)
  - Box 1, folder 28 (Box 83, Folder 2119)
  - Box 1, folder 29 (Box 83, Folder 2120)
  - Box 1, folder 30 (Box 83, Folder 2121)
  - Box 1, folder 31 (Box 83, Folder 2122)
  - Box 1, folder 32 (Box 83, Folder 2123)
  - Box 1, folder 33 (Box 83, Folder 2124)
  - Box 1, folder 34 (Box 83, Folder 2125)
  - Box 1, folder 35 (Box 83, Folder 2126)
  - Box 1, folder 36 (Box 83, Folder 2127)
  - Box 1, folder 37 (Box 83, Folder 2128)
  - Box 1, folder 38 (Box 83, Folder 2129)
  - Box 1, folder 39 (Box 83, Folder 2130)
  - Box 2, folder 40 (Box 83, Folder 2131)
  - Box 2, folder 41 (Box 83, Folder 2132)
  - Box 2, folder 42 (Box 83, Folder 2133)
  - Box 2, folder 43 (Box 83, Folder 2134)
  - Box 2, folder 44 (Box 83, Folder 2135)
  - Box 2, folder 45 (Box 83, Folder 2136)
  - Box 2, folder 46 (Box 83, Folder 2137)
  - Box 2, folder 47 (Box 83, Folder 2138)
  - Box 2, folder 48 (Box 83, Folder 2139)
  - Box 2, folder 49 (Box 83, Folder 2140)
  - Box 2, folder 50 (Box 83, Folder 2141)
  - Box 2, folder 51 (Box 83, Folder 2142)
  - Box 2, folder 52 (Box 83, Folder 2143)
  - Box 2, folder 53 (Box 83, Folder 2144)
  - Box 2, folder 54 (Box 83, Folder 2145)
  - Box 2, folder 55 (Box 83, Folder 2146)
  - Box 2, folder 56 (Box 83, Folder 2147)
  - Box 2, folder 57 (Box 83, Folder 2148)
  - Box 2, folder 58 (Box 83, Folder 2149)
  - Box 2, folder 59 (Box 83, Folder 2150)
  - Box 2, folder 60 (Box 83, Folder 2151)
  - Box 2, folder 61 (Box 83, Folder 2152)
  - Box 2, folder 62 (Box 83, Folder 2153)
  - Box 2, folder 63 (Box 83, Folder 2154)
  - Box 2, folder 64 (Box 83, Folder 2155)
  - Box 2, folder 65 (Box 83, Folder 2156)
  - Box 2, folder 66 (Box 83, Folder 2157)
  - Box 2, folder 67 (Box 83, Folder 2158)
  - Box 2, folder 68 (Box 83, Folder 2159)
  - Box 2, folder 69 (Box 83, Folder 2160)
  - Box 2, folder 71 (Box 84, Folder 2161)
  - Box 2, folder 72 (Box 84, Folder 2162)
  - Box 2, folder 73 (Box 84, Folder 2163)
  - Box 2, folder 74 (Box 84, Folder 2164)
  - Box 2, folder 75 (Box 84, Folder 2165)
  - Box 2, folder 77 (Box 84, Folder 2166)
  - Box 2, folder 78 (Box 84, Folder 2167)
  - Box 2, folder 79 (Box 84, Folder 2168)
  - Box 2, folder 80 (Box 84, Folder 2169)
  - Box 3, folder 81 (Box 84, Folder 2170)
  - Box 3, folder 82 (Box 84, Folder 2171)
  - Box 3, folder 83 (Box 84, Folder 2172)
  - Box 3, folder 84 (Box 84, Folder 2173)
  - Box 3, folder 85 (Box 84, Folder 2174)
  - Box 3, folder 86 (Box 84, Folder 2175)
  - Box 3, folder 87 (Box 84, Folder 2176)
  - Box 3, folder 88 (Box 84, Folder 2177)
  - Box 3, folder 89 (Box 84, Folder 2178)
  - Box 3, folder 90 (Box 84, Folder 2179)
  - Box 3, folder 91 (Box 84, Folder 2180)
  - Box 3, folder 92 (Box 84, Folder 2181)
  - Box 3, folder 93 (Box 84, Folder 2182)
  - Box 3, folder 94 (Box 84, Folder 2183)
  - Box 3, folder 95 (Box 84, Folder 2184)
  - Box 3, folder 96 (Box 84, Folder 2185)
  - Box 3, folder 96a (Box 84, Folder 2186)
  - Box 3, folder 97 (Box 84, Folder 2187)
  - Box 3, folder 99 (Box 84, Folder 2188)
  - Box 3, folder 100 (Box 84, Folder 2189)
  - Box 3, folder 101 (Box 85, Folder 2190)
  - Box 3, folder 102 (Box 85, Folder 2191)
  - Box 3, folder 103 (Box 85, Folder 2192)